<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
  <DreamersDream.DreamDef Name="TerrorisingDream" Abstract="True" ParentName = "BaseDream">
    <tags><li>Terrorising</li></tags>
  </DreamersDream.DreamDef>

  <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "TerrorisingDream">
    <defName>SleepParalysisDream</defName>
    <stages>
      <li>
        <label>Dark figure attacked during sleep</label>
        <description>Some dark figure was sitting on my chest while I slept and I couldn't move!</description>
        <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
      </li>
    </stages>
  </DreamersDream.DreamDef>

  <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "TerrorisingDream">
    <defName>PileCorpsesDream</defName>
    <stages>
      <li>
        <label>Dreamt about pile of corpses</label>
        <description>I way lying on a huge pile of human corpses, some rotten, some fresh. I couldn't move. It was some kind of cargo section inside of a ship in the sea. From the pile crawled a rotten corpse and he grabbed my feet and bit off some toes. He crawled closer and tried to bite... well... that place... I woke up with pain in that place... ~Backrevol</description>
        <baseMoodEffect>-7</baseMoodEffect>
      </li>
    </stages>
    <requirements>
      <li>nonbloodlust</li>
      <li>nonpsychopath</li>
      <li>noncannibal</li>
    </requirements>
  </DreamersDream.DreamDef>

  <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "TerrorisingDream">
    <defName>DreamBrainJars</defName>
    <stages>
      <li>
        <label>Dreamt about a brains in a glass jar</label>
        <description>I was in the middle of some kind of secret archotech laboratory. All floors and walls were sterile. I explored the place for a while until I reached a warehouse which looked like it was hundreds of miles long. On every shelf there was a jar with brain with connected screen to it. I watched what was happening on those screens... someone was cooking meal... someone else was chased by some gangsters... someone else had sex... but then I saw truly extraordinary screen. Screen that was showing perspective of a man in a huge warehouse filled with jars with brains... </description>
        <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
      </li>
    </stages>
  </DreamersDream.DreamDef>

  <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "TerrorisingDream">
    <defName>DreamKillingPet</defName>
    <stages>
      <li>
        <label>Dreamt about killing my favourite animal</label>
        <description>I had to kill my pet by strangling it, I was squeezing its little throat with both hands and it wouldn't die and just kept looking at me with its big green eyes. I was sobbing uncontrollably in the dream but I had to just keep trying to kill it.</description>
        <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
      </li>
    </stages>
    <requirements>
      <li>nonbloodlust</li>
      <li>nonpsychopath</li>
    </requirements>
    <dreamedBy>Slavidor</dreamedBy>
  </DreamersDream.DreamDef>

  <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "TerrorisingDream">
    <defName>DreamMeatLocker</defName>
    <stages>
      <li>
        <label>Dreamt about meat locker</label>
        <description>I was exploring our colony in the dark when I stumbled into the freezer. I saw shapes in the heavy mist hanging on meat hooks, and when I drew close I saw they were human bodies. They reached for me and I tried to turn away but there were more behind me, possessing the faces of people we've killed. They grabbed me and lift me onto a hook to stay there with them for all eternity...</description>
        <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
      </li>
    </stages>
    <requirements>
      <li>nonbloodlust</li>
      <li>nonpsychopath</li>
      <li>noncannibal</li>
    </requirements>
    <dreamedBy>Jack_Hazardous</dreamedBy>
  </DreamersDream.DreamDef>


</Defs>
