<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
 <!--Hell-Like -->
 
  <DreamDarkFigures.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o dark figures</DreamDarkFigures.stages.0.label>
  <DreamDarkFigures.stages.0.description>I was wandering around my place, when I saw shadowy figure coming out of the courner of the room. I asked it what it wants but it didn't respond. The figure was approaching me, being closer and closer with each second. I was panicking, the fear paralysed me. Then another figure appeared behind me. After that the figures grabbed me by my legs and arms. I screamed.</DreamDarkFigures.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamMoonHit.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o moon crash</DreamMoonHit.stages.0.label>
  <DreamMoonHit.stages.0.description>I awoke in my room. Felt a bit thirsty so I went to the kitchen to drink some water. Opened a window to let some fresh air in and there was an enormous moon, everything was shaking, almost like an earthquake was terrorizing the area. Orange light illuminated the surroundings. Buildings were floating here and there, like gravity never existed. The Moon was getting closer. The shaking got stronger. I heard some screams. Then some odd force hit me and I collapsed.</DreamMoonHit.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamTragicLivesAndDeaths.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o tragic lives and deaths</DreamTragicLivesAndDeaths.stages.0.label>
  <DreamTragicLivesAndDeaths.stages.0.description>I had to enter 7 tragical lives of people who had 7 tragical deaths. I lived 7 tragic lives and died 7 tragic deaths. 7... 7... 7..</DreamTragicLivesAndDeaths.stages.0.description>
     
  <!--Terrorising-->
  
  <DreamWorldApart.stages.0.label>Had a dream about Armageddon</DreamWorldApart.stages.0.label>
  <DreamWorldApart.stages.0.description>I dreamt that whole world fell apart. It was a disaster.</DreamWorldApart.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamSleepParalysis.stages.0.label>Dark figure attacked during sleep</DreamSleepParalysis.stages.0.label>
  <DreamSleepParalysis.stages.0.description>Some dark figure was sitting on my chest while I slept and I couldn't move!</DreamSleepParalysis.stages.0.description>
       
  <PileCorpsesDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o pile of corpses</PileCorpsesDream.stages.0.label>
  <PileCorpsesDream.stages.0.description>I way lying on a huge pile of human corpses, some rotten, some fresh. I couldn't move. It was some kind of cargo section inside of a ship in the sea. From the pile crawled a rotten corpse and he grabbed my feet and bit off some toes. He crawled closer and tried to bite... well... that place... I woke up with pain in that place... ~Backrevol</PileCorpsesDream.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamBrainJars.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o a brains in a glass jar</DreamBrainJars.stages.0.label>
  <DreamBrainJars.stages.0.description>I was in the middle of some kind of secret archotech laboratory. All floors and walls were sterile. I explored the place for a while until I reached a warehouse which looked like it was hundreds of miles long. On every shelf there was a jar with brain with connected screen to it. I watched what was happening on those screens... someone was cooking meal... someone else was chased by some gangsters... someone else had sex... but then I saw truly extraordinary screen. Screen that was showing perspective of a man in a huge warehouse filled with jars with brains... </DreamBrainJars.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamMeatLocker.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o meat locker</DreamMeatLocker.stages.0.label>
  <DreamMeatLocker.stages.0.description>I was exploring our colony in the dark when I stumbled into the freezer. I saw shapes in the heavy mist hanging on meat hooks, and when I drew close I saw they were human bodies. They reached for me and I tried to turn away but there were more behind me, possessing the faces of people we've killed. They grabbed me and lift me onto a hook to stay there with them for all eternity...</DreamMeatLocker.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamSpider.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o tiki-spider</DreamSpider.stages.0.label>
  <DreamSpider.stages.0.description>I was in a humid, foreign jungle, trapped in a long ancient stone temple hallway. I turned around, and a spider with a tiki mask started chasing me. I woke up just before it pounced...</DreamSpider.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamMaze.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o escaping a maze</DreamMaze.stages.0.label>
  <DreamMaze.stages.0.description>I was running on what looked like hard packed dirt with little bits of graven and grass. As I ran I would often times have to make decisions on where to run, left or right, because the walls that blocked the way where clown and doll heads. I had to run a maze that was made out of clown and doll head, while something chased me. I woke up and was is a dry sweat and didn't want to open my eyes at all.</DreamMaze.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamFriendsFight.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o fight among friends</DreamFriendsFight.stages.0.label>
  <DreamFriendsFight.stages.0.description>Me and my best friend met in front of his house. We wanted to go biking together, and so we did. We were biking around many different places. When we were finally coming back home we saw a bunch of alligators climbing on a fence next to us. Scared, we biked away as fast as we could. After some time it got really cold outside, so we stopped under someone's house so we could dress up into heavier clothes. Suddenly, out of nowhere a tank appeared and shot at us. My best mate escaped with his bike leaving me alone. Sometime later I woke up at a house. It was the same house we stopped at to dress up. An old man was the owner and he was actually nice. My phone's battery was completely dead though. I wanted to go back home with my bike, but it was in pieces and some were missing. I walked home to tell my parents what happened. When I came back for my bike my other friends were taking it apart for parts. I had to fight them for my bike.</DreamFriendsFight.stages.0.description>
    
  <DreamWerewolfMarriage.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o unfortunate marriage</DreamWerewolfMarriage.stages.0.label>
  <DreamWerewolfMarriage.stages.0.description>I was in a small church, getting married to my ex who passed away years ago. My family was sitting on one side of the room, and the other side was where my ex's family was. The pastor was giving the ceremony, and we were holding hands, looking at each other. At one point, I slowly looked over to both our families. Nothing seemed out of the ordinary. Everything was fine. My family was sitting in the pews, as normal, my ex's as well. After looking at them, I looked at my ex. A few seconds later, I looked back at the families, and noticed something odd. Ex's family has changed into a random menagerie of canines. My family, was completely unphased. I look back at my ex which turned into greyish black werewolf, smirking, still holding my hands.</DreamWerewolfMarriage.stages.0.description>
    
  <DreamPolishVillage.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o polish town</DreamPolishVillage.stages.0.label>
  <DreamPolishVillage.stages.0.description>I was a teenager in a town of Zakątek. My father was an owner of a japanese-style inn, built many years ago by a man who was obsessed with Japan. It was summer and the usual fog rolled in - the fog that made all of our powers stronger. My power of reinforcement magic helped in many incidents around town. Many youths go wild with their boosted powers so fights, petty theft or even small fires are to be expected. But this time, people were disappearing. Specifically, people who stayed at our inn. Strangers. We don't use magic on strangers. We try to hide it from strangers. But someone was kidnapping them. And we found the corpses. Mutilated except for their faces. Then not just the strangers went missing. Our girls too. All of them pretty. Their faces still preserved in their beauty when they were found.</DreamPolishVillage.stages.0.description>
     
  <DreamMazeChildhood.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o abandoned maze</DreamMazeChildhood.stages.0.label>
  <DreamMazeChildhood.stages.0.description>I wandered around a labyrinth of rooms and hallways made up of my childhood home and locations I had previously visited, like my school and my friend's and family's houses.Everything was in black and white, and I had the feeling of being followed, or even chased at times. The rooms always looked run down, like they had been abandoned...</DreamMazeChildhood.stages.0.description>
       
  <DwarfAmbushDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o little dwarf</DwarfAmbushDream.stages.0.label>
  <DwarfAmbushDream.stages.0.description>I dreamt I walked around the forest with my friend and a little dwarf ambushed us and stabbed my friend with a tiny knife!</DwarfAmbushDream.stages.0.description>
     
  <DreamColonyDestruction.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o destruction of colony</DreamColonyDestruction.stages.0.label>
  <DreamColonyDestruction.stages.0.description>I was driving away from the colony I lived in. I had felt a strong sense of urgency, that I needed to get away yet I couldn't figure out why. As I walked up to the hill overlooking my home, I started to calm. As I reached the top, I sat down upon the grass under the trees and watched calmly as a small figure fell down from the boundless, blue sky. Only then, as the antigrain warhead went off did I understand why I felt that urgency.</DreamColonyDestruction.stages.0.description>
       
  <DreamKillingPet.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o killing my favourite animal</DreamKillingPet.stages.0.label>
  <DreamKillingPet.stages.0.description>I had to kill my pet by strangling it, I was squeezing its little throat with both hands and it wouldn't die and just kept looking at me with its big green eyes. I was sobbing uncontrollably in the dream but I had to just keep trying to kill it.</DreamKillingPet.stages.0.description>
       
  <LostHeadDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o distant danger</LostHeadDream.stages.0.label>
  <LostHeadDream.stages.0.description>I had a dream in which I walked around the colony. After a few moments I realised that my head was rolling down the hill away from our home. I chased it until it stopped. After finally regaining my precious head, I looked around. Everything was burned to the ground and the only sounds were coming from strange machinery spitting out mechanoids...</LostHeadDream.stages.0.description>
       
  <KillSomeoneCloseDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o killing a close one</KillSomeoneCloseDream.stages.0.label>
  <KillSomeoneCloseDream.stages.0.description>I killed a person close to me in my dream.</KillSomeoneCloseDream.stages.0.description>
      
  <CannibalismDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o eating humans</CannibalismDream.stages.0.label>
  <CannibalismDream.stages.0.description>I was forced to eat someone in my dream. It was an awful experience...</CannibalismDream.stages.0.description>
        
  <NightmareDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o being chased</NightmareDream.stages.0.label>
  <NightmareDream.stages.0.description>Something was chasing me but I couldn't run!</NightmareDream.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamZombieFight.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o fighting zombies</DreamZombieFight.stages.0.label>
  <DreamZombieFight.stages.0.description>Our colony had to defend against zombies using some ancient non-lethal weaponry. Why would you even use non-lethal weapons?!</DreamZombieFight.stages.0.description>
       
  <HoneyDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o stealing honey</HoneyDream.stages.0.label>
  <HoneyDream.stages.0.description>I was in some kind of magical forest. After walking a few miles I noticed big bee hive. I was hungry, so I put my hand in it to snatch some honey but when I took it out there was no honey... but maggots.</HoneyDream.stages.0.description>
    
  <!--Disturbing -->
 
  <DreamBanditCowboy.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o bandit cowboy</DreamBanditCowboy.stages.0.label>
  <DreamBanditCowboy.stages.0.description> A cowboy was calling on a radio. The entire colony gathered to chat with him. Half were charmed by his outlandish tales, half felt he was sketchy. He wanted to join, together with his giant boomalope. After a long discussion, he was refused, but he still insisted on passing through the colony. He led the boomalope through our fields and when he was in the middle of our crops, near the windmills... he released the 'lope and ran like hell. Then came the bandits. He was part of the bandits... and the boomalope exploding was the sign for the attack. </DreamBanditCowboy.stages.0.description>
      
  <PTSDDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o event from the past</PTSDDream.stages.0.label>
  <PTSDDream.stages.0.description>I had a dream about a stressful event from my past...</PTSDDream.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamSnake.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o being devoured by snake</DreamSnake.stages.0.label>
  <DreamSnake.stages.0.description>I was slowly being devoured by a gigantic snake!</DreamSnake.stages.0.description>
     
  <KillSomeoneDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o killing</KillSomeoneDream.stages.0.label>
  <KillSomeoneDream.stages.0.description>I was killing... But I didn't want to...</KillSomeoneDream.stages.0.description>
      
  <DisturbedSleepStarvation.stages.0.label>Disturbed sleep (starvation)</DisturbedSleepStarvation.stages.0.label>
  <DisturbedSleepStarvation.stages.0.description>My growling stomach kept me awake in the night...</DisturbedSleepStarvation.stages.0.description>
     
  <HungerDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o starvation</HungerDream.stages.0.label>
  <HungerDream.stages.0.description>I was starving... I was begging people to help me... But they wouldn't!</HungerDream.stages.0.description>
      
  <PrisonerDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o being in prison</PrisonerDream.stages.0.label>
  <PrisonerDream.stages.0.description>I was asking them to let me out... I was innocent...</PrisonerDream.stages.0.description>
     
  <ChildhoodBadDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o childhood</ChildhoodBadDream.stages.0.label>
  <ChildhoodBadDream.stages.0.description>I relived some of the worst moments from my childhood.</ChildhoodBadDream.stages.0.description>
     
  <InsectsDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o insects</InsectsDream.stages.0.label>
  <InsectsDream.stages.0.description>They were crawling everywhere. Millions of bugs and worms were chasing me. I woke up the moment they got me...</InsectsDream.stages.0.description>
      
  <InjuryDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o injury</InjuryDream.stages.0.label>
  <InjuryDream.stages.0.description>I had wounds all over my body. Someone hurt me pretty badly but I managed to escape.</InjuryDream.stages.0.description>
     
  <ExclusionDrugDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o social exclusion</ExclusionDrugDream.stages.0.label>
  <ExclusionDrugDream.stages.0.description>In my dream I was excluded from my friendship group because I was scared to snort Yayo...</ExclusionDrugDream.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamZombieTrucks.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o zombie trucks</DreamZombieTrucks.stages.0.label>
  <DreamZombieTrucks.stages.0.description>I was chased across an arid shrubland by zombified monster trucks that had emerged from a cave in a mountain...</DreamZombieTrucks.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamExecution.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o being executed</DreamExecution.stages.0.label>
  <DreamExecution.stages.0.description>My head rolled on the ground for a long time after being swiftly disconnected from my body...</DreamExecution.stages.0.description>
       
  <!--Unpleasent-->
  
  <DreamTornado.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o tornado</DreamTornado.stages.0.label>
  <DreamTornado.stages.0.description>I had a dream where I was in a brick building and it got hit by a tornado. It pulled the building apart and picked me up into the air!</DreamTornado.stages.0.description>
      
  <NoRememberBadDream.stages.0.label>Can't recall a bad dream</NoRememberBadDream.stages.0.label>
  <NoRememberBadDream.stages.0.description>I dreamt about something upsetting but I don't really remember what it was...</NoRememberBadDream.stages.0.description>
       
  <GibberishDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o silly things</GibberishDream.stages.0.label>
  <GibberishDream.stages.0.description>Dancing nuns, walking sofas, talking plants... I dreamt about weird things, nothing in particular but it didn't feel good.</GibberishDream.stages.0.description>
       
  <NakedSchoolDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o naked walking</NakedSchoolDream.stages.0.label>
  <NakedSchoolDream.stages.0.description>I was walking around school, when I realised that I'm wearing no clothes! I felt so embarrased when all my friends were laughing at me! ~Toast</NakedSchoolDream.stages.0.description>
        
  <ExDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o my ex partners</ExDream.stages.0.label>
  <ExDream.stages.0.description>I don't want you back in my life! Stop bothering me in my sleep!</ExDream.stages.0.description>
       
  <NakedColonyDream.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o naked walking</NakedColonyDream.stages.0.label>
  <NakedColonyDream.stages.0.description>I was walking around our colony, when I realised that I'm wearing no clothes! I felt so embarrased when all the other other colonists were laughing at me!</NakedColonyDream.stages.0.description>
       
  <DreamFlamingoInvasion.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o flamingos invasion</DreamFlamingoInvasion.stages.0.label>
  <DreamFlamingoInvasion.stages.0.description>The world got invaded by flamingos. The flamingos had kevlar helmets, assault rifles, demonic red eyes, and they were sometimes doing drill movements.</DreamFlamingoInvasion.stages.0.description>
      
  <DreamMindControl.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o being mind controlled</DreamMindControl.stages.0.label>
  <DreamMindControl.stages.0.description>People around me were getting injected with mind control drugs forcefully.</DreamMindControl.stages.0.description>
       
  <DreamAnxiety.stages.0.label>Disturbed sleep (anxiety)</DreamAnxiety.stages.0.label>
  <DreamAnxiety.stages.0.description>I was stressed and I could not stop thinking. Will those worries ever end?</DreamAnxiety.stages.0.description>
       
  <!--Sleepwalks -->
  
  <SleepwalkRedheadWithBeard.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o redhead with beard</SleepwalkRedheadWithBeard.stages.0.label>
  <SleepwalkRedheadWithBeard.stages.0.description>It started off at school, where I began to realize something was wrong. Everyone I saw looked like they could barely contain themselves from instantly becoming violent, and they had this look in their eyes like they had just spotted the best prey they had ever seen, but were held back by something. I remember thinking "No way, I'm out", and ran home as fast as I could. Some of it is blurry, but I remember coming across people that I knew, either friends or family, or people from the neighborhood, telling me to get home, that it's not safe. Finally I make it there, put the key in the front door, open it, and I am literally surrounded by all of those same people, only now they look like the ones at school, and there stands the redhead with the beard. Without saying a word she lunges at me and pierces my neck with her fangs. </SleepwalkRedheadWithBeard.stages.0.description>
       
  <SleepwalkShapes.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o abstract shapes</SleepwalkShapes.stages.0.label>
  <SleepwalkShapes.stages.0.description>I saw many abstract shapes that were floating around me like planets. I thought the shapes were my family and friends. At some point a foreign shape appeared consuming my close ones and thus growing bigger. At the end it got me too... </SleepwalkShapes.stages.0.description>
      
  <SleepwalkSteps.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o strange steps</SleepwalkSteps.stages.0.label>
  <SleepwalkSteps.stages.0.description>I dreamt about a strange cavern with hundreds of steps. I knew some other world existed down there but it was too far for me to reach. With each step I took towards it the cavern got smaller and smaller. At some point it disappeared... and I was all alone in the dark.</SleepwalkSteps.stages.0.description>
       
  <SleepwalkFurniture.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o furniture</SleepwalkFurniture.stages.0.label>
  <SleepwalkFurniture.stages.0.description>All of the furniture pieces around me started to grow and at some point they were as tall as old buildings in books. I knew they were evil... I had to fight them!</SleepwalkFurniture.stages.0.description>
      
  <SleepwalkDarkness.stages.0.label>{0_gender ? Śniłem : Śniłam} o darkness</SleepwalkDarkness.stages.0.label>
  <SleepwalkDarkness.stages.0.description>There was darkness all around me... There was light somewhere but I didn't know where, so I searched for it. Without the light there was no hope...</SleepwalkDarkness.stages.0.description>
       

</LanguageData>