<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Defs>
    <!--Hell-Like -->
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="HellLikeDream">
        <defName>DreamDarkFigures</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about dark figures</label>
                <description>I was wandering around my place, when I saw shadowy figure coming out
                    of the courner of the room. I asked it what it wants but it didn't respond. The
                    figure was approaching me, being closer and closer with each second. I was
                    panicking, the fear paralysed me. Then another figure appeared behind me. After
                    that the figures grabbed me by my legs and arms. I screamed.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-11</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>fan</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="HellLikeDream">
        <defName>DreamMoonHit</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about moon crash</label>
                <description>I awoke in my room. Felt a bit thirsty so I went to the kitchen to
                    drink some water. Opened a window to let some fresh air in and there was an
                    enormous moon, everything was shaking, almost like an earthquake was terrorizing
                    the area. Orange light illuminated the surroundings. Buildings were floating
                    here and there, like gravity never existed. The Moon was getting closer. The
                    shaking got stronger. I heard some screams. Then some odd force hit me and I
                    collapsed.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-11</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>Backrevol</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="HellLikeDream">
        <defName>DreamTragicLivesAndDeaths</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about tragic lives and deaths</label>
                <description>I had to enter 7 tragical lives of people who had 7 tragical deaths. I
                    lived 7 tragic lives and died 7 tragic deaths. 7... 7... 7..</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-11</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <tags>
            <li>Nonpsycho</li>
        </tags>
        <dreamedBy>dambuk1</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <!--Terrorising-->
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="TerrorisingDream">
        <defName>DreamWorldApart</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Had a dream about Armageddon</label>
                <description>I dreamt that whole world fell apart. It was a disaster.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="TerrorisingDream">
        <defName>DreamSleepParalysis</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dark figure attacked during sleep</label>
                <description>Some dark figure was sitting on my chest while I slept and I couldn't
                    move!</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="TerrorisingDream">
        <defName>PileCorpsesDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about pile of corpses</label>
                <description>I way lying on a huge pile of human corpses, some rotten, some fresh. I
                    couldn't move. It was some kind of cargo section inside of a ship in the sea.
                    From the pile crawled a rotten corpse and he grabbed my feet and bit off some
                    toes. He crawled closer and tried to bite... well... that place... I woke up
                    with pain in that place... ~Backrevol</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <tags>
            <li>Nonpsycho</li>
            <li>Noncannibal</li>
        </tags>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="TerrorisingDream">
        <defName>DreamBrainJars</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about a brains in a glass jar</label>
                <description>I was in the middle of some kind of secret archotech laboratory. All
                    floors and walls were sterile. I explored the place for a while until I reached
                    a warehouse which looked like it was hundreds of miles long. On every shelf
                    there was a jar with brain with connected screen to it. I watched what was
                    happening on those screens... someone was cooking meal... someone else was
                    chased by some gangsters... someone else had sex... but then I saw truly
                    extraordinary screen. Screen that was showing perspective of a man in a huge
                    warehouse filled with jars with brains... </description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="TerrorisingDream">
        <defName>DreamMeatLocker</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about meat locker</label>
                <description>I was exploring our colony in the dark when I stumbled into the
                    freezer. I saw shapes in the heavy mist hanging on meat hooks, and when I drew
                    close I saw they were human bodies. They reached for me and I tried to turn away
                    but there were more behind me, possessing the faces of people we've killed. They
                    grabbed me and lift me onto a hook to stay there with them for all
                    eternity...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <tags>
            <li>Nonpsycho</li>
            <li>Noncannibal</li>
        </tags>
        <dreamedBy>Jack_Hazardous</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="TerrorisingDream">
        <defName>DreamSpider</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about tiki-spider</label>
                <description>I was in a humid, foreign jungle, trapped in a long ancient stone
                    temple hallway. I turned around, and a spider with a tiki mask started chasing
                    me. I woke up just before it pounced...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>ryanizawsum</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="TerrorisingDream">
        <defName>DreamMaze</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about escaping a maze</label>
                <description>I was running on what looked like hard packed dirt with little bits of
                    graven and grass. As I ran I would often times have to make decisions on where
                    to run, left or right, because the walls that blocked the way where clown and
                    doll heads. I had to run a maze that was made out of clown and doll head, while
                    something chased me. I woke up and was is a dry sweat and didn't want to open my
                    eyes at all.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>NylonWorms</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="TerrorisingDream">
        <defName>DreamFriendsFight</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about fight among friends</label>
                <description>Me and my best friend met in front of his house. We wanted to go biking
                    together, and so we did. We were biking around many different places. When we
                    were finally coming back home we saw a bunch of alligators climbing on a fence
                    next to us. Scared, we biked away as fast as we could. After some time it got
                    really cold outside, so we stopped under someone's house so we could dress up
                    into heavier clothes. Suddenly, out of nowhere a tank appeared and shot at us.
                    My best mate escaped with his bike leaving me alone. Sometime later I woke up at
                    a house. It was the same house we stopped at to dress up. An old man was the
                    owner and he was actually nice. My phone's battery was completely dead though. I
                    wanted to go back home with my bike, but it was in pieces and some were missing.
                    I walked home to tell my parents what happened. When I came back for my bike my
                    other friends were taking it apart for parts. I had to fight them for my
                    bike.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>Smelly Fish</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="TerrorisingDream">
        <defName>DreamWerewolfMarriage</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about unfortunate marriage</label>
                <description>I was in a small church, getting married to my ex who passed away years
                    ago. My family was sitting on one side of the room, and the other side was where
                    my ex's family was. The pastor was giving the ceremony, and we were holding
                    hands, looking at each other. At one point, I slowly looked over to both our
                    families. Nothing seemed out of the ordinary. Everything was fine. My family was
                    sitting in the pews, as normal, my ex's as well. After looking at them, I looked
                    at my ex. A few seconds later, I looked back at the families, and noticed
                    something odd. Ex's family has changed into a random menagerie of canines. My
                    family, was completely unphased. I look back at my ex which turned into greyish
                    black werewolf, smirking, still holding my hands.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>Lt. Vulfskrag</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <!--Frightening-->
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>DreamPolishVillage</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Colonist</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about polish town</label>
                <description>I was a teenager in a town of Zakątek. My father was an owner of a
                    japanese-style inn, built many years ago by a man who was obsessed with Japan.
                    It was summer and the usual fog rolled in - the fog that made all of our powers
                    stronger. My power of reinforcement magic helped in many incidents around town.
                    Many youths go wild with their boosted powers so fights, petty theft or even
                    small fires are to be expected. But this time, people were disappearing.
                    Specifically, people who stayed at our inn. Strangers. We don't use magic on
                    strangers. We try to hide it from strangers. But someone was kidnapping them.
                    And we found the corpses. Mutilated except for their faces. Then not just the
                    strangers went missing. Our girls too. All of them pretty. Their faces still
                    preserved in their beauty when they were found.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-5</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>dambuk1</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>DreamMazeChildhood</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about abandoned maze</label>
                <description>I wandered around a labyrinth of rooms and hallways made up of my
                    childhood home and locations I had previously visited, like my school and my
                    friend's and family's houses. Everything was in black and white, and I had the
                    feeling of being followed, or even chased at times. The rooms always looked run
                    down, like they had been abandoned...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-5</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>GHOST</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>DwarfAmbushDream</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Nonpsycho</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about little dwarf</label>
                <description>I dreamt I walked around the forest with my friend and a little dwarf
                    ambushed us and stabbed my friend with a tiny knife!</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-5</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>DreamColonyDestruction</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Colonist</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about destruction of colony</label>
                <description>I was driving away from the colony I lived in. I had felt a strong
                    sense of urgency, that I needed to get away yet I couldn't figure out why. As I
                    walked up to the hill overlooking my home, I started to calm. As I reached the
                    top, I sat down upon the grass under the trees and watched calmly as a small
                    figure fell down from the boundless, blue sky. Only then, as the antigrain
                    warhead went off did I understand why I felt that urgency.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-5</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>Wight</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>DreamKillingPet</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about killing my favourite animal</label>
                <description>I had to kill my pet by strangling it, I was squeezing its little
                    throat with both hands and it wouldn't die and just kept looking at me with its
                    big green eyes. I was sobbing uncontrollably in the dream but I had to just keep
                    trying to kill it.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-5</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <tags>
            <li>Nonpsycho</li>
        </tags>
        <dreamedBy>Slavidor</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>LostHeadDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about distant danger</label>
                <description>I had a dream in which I walked around the colony. After a few moments
                    I realised that my head was rolling down the hill away from our home. I chased
                    it until it stopped. After finally regaining my precious head, I looked around.
                    Everything was burned to the ground and the only sounds were coming from strange
                    machinery spitting out mechanoids...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-5</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>KillSomeoneCloseDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about killing a close one</label>
                <description>I killed a person close to me in my dream.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-5</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <tags>
            <li>Nonpsycho</li>
        </tags>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>CannibalismDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about eating humans</label>
                <description>I was forced to eat someone in my dream. It was an awful
                    experience...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-5</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <tags>
            <li>Nonpsycho</li>
            <li>Noncannibal</li>
        </tags>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>NightmareDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about being chased</label>
                <description>Something was chasing me but I couldn't run!</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-5</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>DreamZombieFight</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Colonist</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about fighting zombies</label>
                <description>Our colony had to defend against zombies using some ancient non-lethal
                    weaponry. Why would you even use non-lethal weapons?!</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-5</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>Maru1i</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>HoneyDream</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Stressed</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about stealing honey</label>
                <description>I was in some kind of magical forest. After walking a few miles I
                    noticed big bee hive. I was hungry, so I put my hand in it to snatch some honey
                    but when I took it out there was no honey... but maggots.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-5</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>

    <!--Disturbing -->
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>DreamBanditCowboy</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Colonist</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about bandit cowboy</label>
                <description> A cowboy was calling on a radio. The entire colony gathered to chat
                    with him. Half were charmed by his outlandish tales, half felt he was sketchy.
                    He wanted to join, together with his giant boomalope. After a long discussion,
                    he was refused, but he still insisted on passing through the colony. He led the
                    boomalope through our fields and when he was in the middle of our crops, near
                    the windmills... he released the 'lope and ran like hell. Then came the bandits.
                    He was part of the bandits... and the boomalope exploding was the sign for the
                    attack. </description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>dambuk1</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>PTSDDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about event from the past</label>
                <description>I had a dream about a stressful event from my past...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>DreamSnake</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about being devoured by snake</label>
                <description>I was slowly being devoured by a gigantic snake!</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>Djura</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>KillSomeoneDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about killing</label>
                <description>I was killing... But I didn't want to...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <tags>
            <li>Nonpsycho</li>
        </tags>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>DisturbedSleepStarvation</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Disturbed sleep (starvation)</label>
                <description>My growling stomach kept me awake in the night...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <tags>
            <li>Starving</li>
        </tags>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>HungerDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about starvation</label>
                <description>I was starving... I was begging people to help me... But they
                    wouldn't!</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <tags>
            <li>Full</li>
        </tags>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>PrisonerDream</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Colonist</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about being in prison</label>
                <description>I was asking them to let me out... I was innocent...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>ChildhoodBadDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about childhood</label>
                <description>I relived some of the worst moments from my childhood.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>InsectsDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about insects</label>
                <description>They were crawling everywhere. Millions of bugs and worms were chasing
                    me. I woke up the moment they got me...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>InjuryDream</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Healthy</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about injury</label>
                <description>I had wounds all over my body. Someone hurt me pretty badly but I
                    managed to escape.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>ExclusionDrugDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about social exclusion</label>
                <description>In my dream I was excluded from my friendship group because I was
                    scared to snort Yayo...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>DreamZombieTrucks</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about zombie trucks</label>
                <description>I was chased across an arid shrubland by zombified monster trucks that
                    had emerged from a cave in a mountain...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>ManaVeil</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>DreamExecution</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Prisoner</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about being executed</label>
                <description>My head rolled on the ground for a long time after being swiftly
                    disconnected from my body...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>Denneisk</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <!--Unpleasent-->
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="UnpleasantDream">
        <defName>DreamTornado</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about tornado</label>
                <description>I had a dream where I was in a brick building and it got hit by a
                    tornado. It pulled the building apart and picked me up into the
                    air!</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-2</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>Gallivant</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="UnpleasantDream">
        <defName>NoRememberBadDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Can't recall a bad dream</label>
                <description>I dreamt about something upsetting but I don't really remember what it
                    was...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-1</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="UnpleasantDream">
        <defName>GibberishDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about silly things</label>
                <description>Dancing nuns, walking sofas, talking plants... I dreamt about weird
                    things, nothing in particular but it didn't feel good.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-2</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="UnpleasantDream">
        <defName>NakedSchoolDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about naked walking</label>
                <description>I was walking around school, when I realised that I'm wearing no
                    clothes! I felt so embarrased when all my friends were laughing at me!
                    ~Toast</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-2</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="UnpleasantDream">
        <defName>ExDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about my ex partners</label>
                <description>I don't want you back in my life! Stop bothering me in my
                    sleep!</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-2</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="UnpleasantDream">
        <defName>NakedColonyDream</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about naked walking</label>
                <description>I was walking around our colony, when I realised that I'm wearing no
                    clothes! I felt so embarrased when all the other other colonists were laughing
                    at me!</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-2</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <tags>
            <li>Colonist</li>
        </tags>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="UnpleasantDream">
        <defName>DreamFlamingoInvasion</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about flamingos invasion</label>
                <description>The world got invaded by flamingos. The flamingos had kevlar helmets,
                    assault rifles, demonic red eyes, and they were sometimes doing drill
                    movements.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-2</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>CaucasianMalaysian</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="UnpleasantDream">
        <defName>DreamMindControl</defName>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about being mind controlled</label>
                <description>People around me were getting injected with mind control drugs
                    forcefully.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-2</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>Denneisk</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="UnpleasantDream">
        <defName>DreamAnxiety</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Stressed</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Disturbed sleep (anxiety)</label>
                <description>I was stressed and I could not stop thinking. Will those worries ever
                    end?</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-2</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>Denneisk</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <!--Sleepwalks -->
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="TerrorisingDream">
        <defName>SleepwalkRedheadWithBeard</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Sleepwalk</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about redhead with beard</label>
                <description>It started off at school, where I began to realize something was wrong.
                    Everyone I saw looked like they could barely contain themselves from instantly
                    becoming violent, and they had this look in their eyes like they had just
                    spotted the best prey they had ever seen, but were held back by something. I
                    remember thinking "No way, I'm out", and ran home as fast as I could. Some of it
                    is blurry, but I remember coming across people that I knew, either friends or
                    family, or people from the neighborhood, telling me to get home, that it's not
                    safe. Finally I make it there, put the key in the front door, open it, and I am
                    literally surrounded by all of those same people, only now they look like the
                    ones at school, and there stands the redhead with the beard. Without saying a
                    word she lunges at me and pierces my neck with her fangs. </description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
        <dreamedBy>Rinzler0001</dreamedBy>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>SleepwalkShapes</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Sleepwalk</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about abstract shapes</label>
                <description>I saw many abstract shapes that were floating around me like planets. I
                    thought the shapes were my family and friends. At some point a foreign shape
                    appeared consuming my close ones and thus growing bigger. At the end it got me
                    too... </description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-6</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>SleepwalkSteps</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Sleepwalk</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about strange steps</label>
                <description>I dreamt about a strange cavern with hundreds of steps. I knew some
                    other world existed down there but it was too far for me to reach. With each
                    step I took towards it the cavern got smaller and smaller. At some point it
                    disappeared... and I was all alone in the dark.</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-4</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="FrighteningDream">
        <defName>SleepwalkFurniture</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Sleepwalk</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about furniture</label>
                <description>All of the furniture pieces around me started to grow and at some point
                    they were as tall as old buildings in books. I knew they were evil... I had to
                    fight them!</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-6</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="DisturbingDream">
        <defName>SleepwalkDarkness</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Sleepwalk</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about darkness</label>
                <description>There was darkness all around me... There was light somewhere but I
                    didn't know where, so I searched for it. Without the light there was no
                    hope...</description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef>

    <!-- New Dreams -->
</Defs>
<!--     
    <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName="BaseDream">
        <defName>DreamGeneric</defName>
        <tags>
            <li>Colonist</li>
        </tags>
        <stages>
            <li>
                <label>Dreamt about darkness</label>
                <description> A cowboy was calling on a radio. The entire colony gathered to chat
                    with him. Half were charmed by his outlandish tales, half felt he was sketchy.
                    He wanted to join, together with his giant boomalope. After a long discussion,
                    he was refused, but he still insisted on passing through the colony. He led the
                    boomalope through our fields and when he was in the middle of our crops, near
                    the windmills... he released the 'lope and ran like hell. Then came the bandits.
                    He was part of the bandits... and the boomalope exploding was the sign for the
                    attack. </description>
                <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
            </li>
        </stages>
    </DreamersDream.DreamDef> 


-->
<!--
<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "BaseDream">
  <defName>TravelDreamUlthar</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>ulthar dream</label>
      <description>I had a dream I visited a town full of cats! </description>
      <baseMoodEffect>6</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "BaseDream">
  <defName>TravelDreamKadath</defName>
  <chance>0.1</chance>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>kadath dream</label>
      <description>Kadath... Chaos... Where was I...?</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-10</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "BaseDream">
  <defName>TravelDreamCelephais</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>celephais dream</label>
      <description>I have visited a city full of gold and where everything is forever young!</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>8</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "BaseDream">
  <defName>TravelDreamMoon</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>moon dream</label>
      <description>I dreamed I've been kidnapped by disgusting creatures from the moon!</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "BaseDream">
  <defName>TravelDreamLeng</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>moon dream</label>
      <description>I visited horrible and cold place full of man eating humanlike creatures.</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "BaseDream">
  <defName>TravelDreamEnchantedForest</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>forest dream</label>
      <description>I visited horrible and cold place full of spiders and awful looking </description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-8</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "BaseDream">
  <defName>ImplantGlitchDream</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>Had a dream about childhood</label>
      <description>I relived some of the worst moments from my childhood.</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-4</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
  <sensitivities>
    <li>ill</li>
    <li>hungry</li>
    <li>malnourished</li>
  </sensitivities>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>
-->
