<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
  <DreamersDream.DreamDef Name="DisturbingDream" Abstract="True" ParentName = "BaseDream">
    <tags><li>Disturbing</li></tags>
  </DreamersDream.DreamDef>

  <DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "DisturbingDream">
  <defName>PrisonerDream</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>Dreamt about being in prison</label>
      <description>I was asking them to let me out... I was innocent...</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "DisturbingDream">
  <defName>ChildhoodBadDream</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>Dreamt about childhood</label>
      <description>I relived some of the worst moments from my childhood.</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "DisturbingDream">
  <defName>InsectsDream</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>Dreamt about insects</label>
      <description>They were crawling everywhere. Millions of bugs and worms were chasing me. I woke up the moment they got me...</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "DisturbingDream">
  <defName>InjuryDream</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>Dreamt about injury</label>
      <description>I had wounds all over my body. Someone hurt me pretty badly but I managed to escape.</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "DisturbingDream">
  <defName>HoneyDream</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>Dreamt about stealing honey</label>
      <description>I was in some kind of magical forest. After walking a few miles I noticed big bee hive. I was hungry, so I put my hand in it to snatch some honey but when I took it out there was no honey... but maggots.</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "DisturbingDream">
  <defName>ExclusionDrugDream</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>Dreamt about social exclusion</label>
      <description>In my dream I was excluded from my friendship group because I was scared to snort Yayo...</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>


<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "DisturbingDream">
  <defName>DreamMaze</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>Dreamt about escaping a maze</label>
      <description>I was running on what looked like hard packed dirt with little bits of graven and grass. As I ran I would often times have to make decisions on where to run, left or right, because the walls that blocked the way where clown and doll heads.
I had to run a maze that was made out of clown and doll head, while something chased me. I woke up and was is a dry sweat and didn't want to open my eyes at all.</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
  <dreamedBy>NylonWorms</dreamedBy>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "DisturbingDream">
  <defName>DreamFriendsFight</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>Dreamt about fight among friends</label>
      <description>Me and my best friend met in front of his house. We wanted to go biking together, and so we did. We were biking around many different places. When we were finally coming back home we saw a bunch of alligators climbing on a fence next to us. Scared, we biked away as fast as we could. After some time it got really cold outside, so we stopped under someone's house so we could dress up into heavier clothes. Suddenly, out of nowhere a tank appeared and shot at us. My best mate escaped with his bike leaving me alone.
Sometime later I woke up at a house. It was the same house we stopped at to dress up. An old man was the owner and he was actually nice. My phone's battery was completely dead though. I wanted to go back home with my bike, but it was in pieces and some were missing. I walked home to tell my parents what happened. When I came back for my bike my other friends were taking it apart for parts. I had to fight them for my bike.</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
  <dreamedBy>Smelly Fish</dreamedBy>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "DisturbingDream">
  <defName>DreamColonyDestruction</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>Dreamt about destruction of colony</label>
      <description>I was driving away from the colony I lived in.
I had felt a strong sense of urgency, that I needed to get away yet I couldn't figure out why. As I walkedup to the hill overlooking my home, I started to calm. As I reached the top, I sat down upon the grass under the trees and watched calmly as a small figure fell down from the boundless, blue sky.
Only then, as the antigrain warhead went off did I understand why I felt that urgency.</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-4</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
  <dreamedBy>Wight</dreamedBy>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

<DreamersDream.DreamDef ParentName = "DisturbingDream">
  <defName>DreamWerewolfMarriage</defName>
  <stages>
    <li>
      <label>Dreamt about unfortunate marriage</label>
      <description>I was in a small church, getting married to my ex who passed away years ago. My family was sitting on one side of the room, and the other side was where my ex's family was. The pastor was giving the ceremony, and we were holding hands, looking at each other. At one point, I slowly looked over to both our families. Nothing seemed out of the ordinary. Everything was fine. My family was sitting in the pews, as normal, my ex's as well. After looking at them, I looked at my ex. A few seconds later, I looked back at the families, and noticed something odd. Ex's family has changed into a random menagerie of canines. My family, was completely unphased. I look back at my ex which turned into greyish black werewolf, smirking, still holding my hands.</description>
      <baseMoodEffect>-4</baseMoodEffect>
    </li>
  </stages>
  <dreamedBy>Lt. Vulfskrag</dreamedBy>
</DreamersDream.DreamDef>

</Defs>
